I've been seeing a lot of commentary on this and I just feel the need to also echo it.
If you are now speaking out about ICE and you weren't speaking about Palestine, I want you to know that Palestine and ICE are the same.
It's even the same people. It's the IOF, it's the Israeli Offense Forces.
Now, when you saw what was happening in Palestine, you may have said to yourself, well, that's over there.
And you also may have said to yourself, well, I don't want to say anything because then they're going to say I'm anti-Slamatic.
And you don't want to be called anti-Semitic because, you know, in some cases you may be like, I don't want people to think I don't like Jewish people, which is fair.
Like you don't want to be labeled something you are not.
I think a lot of you also just don't want the drama that comes with that.
Well, guess what? It's happening here now.
Are you anti-Semitic calling out ICE? Because maybe they're coming with that next.
I just want you to know that's coming next.
They're going to, the same way they're calling you Tera Rists.
Yeah.
And I'm watching folks now get some gumption and they think it's separate.
They think it's like, well, now I'm talking about Americans, so it's fine.
Had we been talking about this louder when it was Palestinians,
Americans, maybe, just maybe, we wouldn't even have to be talking about Americans.
We shouldn't even be calling ourselves Americans anyway.
U.S.ians.
We're all slaves, and you love it.
So you deserve what you get, the erosion of your democracy.
You'll soon be the laughing stock of the world.
That works out to less than 50 cents.
It's a damn shame.
That's why the children are occupying space in New York, in Boston, in Washington, in Chicago,
in San Francisco, in other cities.
Why?
Because they're not looking to you as a source of information for them.
Look how long it took you all to talk about what was going on in New York.
It took you two weeks because the same people that controlled the banks controlled the media.
You all know it, but you're afraid to say it.